Contact

Bangladesh +8801736302961 (Mobile) tapos.k.sarker25@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tapos-sarker (LinkedIn) snackstech.blogspot.com/ (Blog)

Top Skills

Web Development Web Design JavaScript

Languages

Bengali (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)
Hindi (Elementary)

Tapos Sarker

Web Designer & Developer Bangladesh

Summary

I'm Tapos Kumar Sarker.

My home town is in Dinajpur, Bangladesh. I am a web designer and developer since 2017. That's nearly 3 years.

In the beginning, I had an interest in everything related to the computer, Like Graphic Design, Video Editing, game development, etc. so learned some of those things. then settled down.

During my 2nd semester in college, I also began Online problemsolving.

As mentioned earlier, I work on Both Frontend & Backend. Raw PHP, OOP PHP language. HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Jquery, Mysql, Laravel, etc. I worked as a web designer for 1 year. Then started Web Developing.

Team Work:

- 1. I am comfortable with Trello to maintain teamwork and Work Management.
- 2. I also use Github For Group Projects, team projects.

Hobby:

Learning new things and Coding, these are the best two terms of my life. I love Coding and development.

Lets Hope For the Best in Future.
Please Message me If You need Any More Info.

Experience

techdynobd Co-Founder March 2018 - Present (2 years 2 months) chairman Bari, Soinik club, Dhaka We create this IT firm from 0. We wanted to start something of our own without investing large amount of Money.

We Started #TECHDYNOBD to apply our skill for better client satisfaction and keep attached to the tech world. And we intend to provide support 24/7

Currently, Our Client Satisfaction rate is 94.8% And growing.

AR Integration And Solution Web Designer And Developer May 2018 - October 2018 (6 months) Jigatola,dhaka,Bangladesh

I joined AR integration and Solution as a web designer and Developer. I spent a memorable 6 months of my life there.

I designed several websites for them in those 6 months. Once, My Boss Russell vai started to teach me python Django. I learned many things from him. Best mentor For me.

I adopted 30% of my Graphics & Business Development thinking skills from him.

We had a Youtube channel Called Riddles Freak. We create this channel to analyze Youtube traffic, Age-based traffic filtration, and fun. We created more than 24 videos and Started to gain subscribers. We worked together while making videos for youtube. that was an enjoyable memory.

WPREDOX

Web Designer-on WordPress Themes October 2017 - December 2017 (3 months)

kallyanpur,dhaka

WPREDOX was a WordPress theme developing Startup. I was a part-time web designer Employe.

Then I was looking forward to working with professionals so I joined them without having previous work experience on Wordpress. It was my 1st job.

Then We mostly used the google drive and dropbox to share 90% of project files. keep our Contact on Google Hangout on vacations.

They Taught me Time Management, Maintain Deadline, etc. I continued office 4.5 hours every day after college.

Self Employed Self Employed June 2017 - October 2017 (5 months) dhaka

I was working as a freelancer on fiver and other Local And Global sectors.

Then I was a graphics designer. I created logos and other stationery concepts for more than 10+ local clients.

I made 3 designs for each client so that they can choose 1 from 3. And that makes them happier.

I spent 4 to 5 hours a day for the client's work and the rest to learn the Basics of new web Technology and Communication Methods.

On average I Served 32 hours to 35 hours a week to local or job portals like Fiverr, freelancer, etc

Education

ISTT

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science (2015 - 2019)

BITM

WEB DESIGNER, Computer and Information Sciences and Support Services · (2017 - 2017)

Pondit

Web development With PHP, Computer and Information Sciences and Support Services · (2018 - 2018)